L2R: agent-assisted correction, recovery data, and policy adaptation. Animated schematic.
RoboDojo: Fill Pen Holder. Selected clips at 3× playback.
Real world: Wash Clothes — policy-only failure recovery.
Autonomous recovery without online Agent control.
Selected clips at 4× / 5× / 4× playback.
RoboDojo: Insert Tubes. Selected clips at 1.5× / 1.25× playback.
Real world: Fridge Organizing — policy-only failure recovery.
Autonomous recovery without online Agent control.
Selected clips at 4× / 4.5× playback.
RoboDojo: Store Laptop & Headphones. Selected clips at 3× playback.
Real world: Hang Up Headphones — policy-only failure recovery.
Autonomous recovery without online Agent control.
Selected clips at 4× / 3× playback.
RoboDojo: Stack Bowls. Selected clips at 2.5× playback.
RoboDojo: Arrange Largest Number. Selected clips at 3× playback.
RoboDojo: Stack Blocks. Selected clips at 2.5× playback.
Learning to Recover: Iteratively Internalizing Agent Corrections into VLAs for Robotic Manipulation.